http://www.marblehill.co.uk/privacy-policy

Call us +44 (0)20 8892 1488 or Contact us here |  Mon to Fri: 10:00am - 5:30pm | Sat: 10am - 5pmHomeBalanced Flue Gas FiresView full rangeBellfiresKalfire Gas firesRais Gas RangeBalanced Flue Gas StovesBio Ethanol FiresFlueless Fires / EkofiresGas Fire ServicingGas Fire Maintenance TipsBalanced Flue TerminalsFrequently Asked QuestionsFireplace MantelsView full rangeStone EnglishHole in the WallAntique MantelsMarble MantelsReproduction FrenchBespoke FireplacesRestorationWood BurnersView full rangeBarbas Wood BurnersKalfire Wood BurnersHwam Wood Burning StovesJetmasterRais Wood BurnersStovax Wood BurnersParkray Wood BurnersElectric FiresFire Baskets & InteriorsFirebasketsRegister GratesAboutAbout usOur BlogTour Our ShowroomsCustomer ReviewsOur BrochureCustomer CareSatisfaction SurveyJob VacanciesComplaint QuestionnaireTechnical SpecificationsGalleryContactPrivacy PolicyHow we collect and use your informationMHF is committed to protecting your personal information. Our Privacy Policy
gives you detailed information on why we collect your personal information, how
we use it and how we keep it secure.  Why we
collect personal data and how we use itGenerally, we collect information from you when you decide to interact
with us. This could be via the website, when you register your details or through
feedback on our products or services. We only collect information that’s
necessary to carry out our business or to provide the particular service you’ve
requested and to keep you informed. This data will only be used to provide a
better customer service and will not be passed on to third parties without your
permission. How we
protect your informationWe adopt robust and appropriate technologies and policies, so the
information we have about you is protected from unauthorized access and
improper use. Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and
known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit as safe as possible. Access
to personal data is controlled through restricted access rights on the server and
any hard copy (printed) data is kept in locked cabinets with restricted access.
All data is encrypted before backup.Your rights to access your informationWe follow the rules and regulations of the General Data Protection
Regulations (GDPR). Under GDPR you have the right to be informed about your
data, to have access to your data, to request that inaccurate data be
corrected, to request data held about you be deleted and to object to
processing of your data.  You also have
the right to data portability. For more information please go to https://ico.org.uk/If you no longer wish to receive emails from MHF and/or you want to be
removed from our database, you can contact info@marblehill.co.uk or select
‘unsubscribe’ from the bottom of the email and your address will be
automatically removed from our database. Use of CookiesCookies are small files that get written to your computer’s hard drive
through your Web Browser (i.e. Google Chrome, Internet Explorer etc.) when you
access information through the web. You will always be notified when this
occurs and you have the option to decline. You can also set the preferences on
your browser to turn off cookies. They are commonly used to analyse your preferences
based on previous or current site activity. This enables us to provide a
better, more tailored service for our customers. We also use cookies to compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction to enable us to offer a
better site experience in the future.What types of cookies do we useAn overview of the cookies used on this website is set out in the following table.Interested in our Fireplaces?As each project is individual we would recommend that you give us a call on 020 8892 1488 to fully discuss your specific set of requirements. Alternatively if you prefer to fill in your phone number below we would be happy to give you a call.Please check the box if you consent to us contacting you regarding our productsThanks for your interest. One of our team will be in touch soon.Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.Call us today on020 8892 1488 to discuss your requirements.AlternativelyFill in our enquiry formLatest NewsHow Modern Fireplaces Improve Home Heating Today’s modern balanced flue gas fireplaces can provide the best of both worlds: complementary style, ambiance, energy-saving features, and an effective source of home heat.October 2019Read articleFeatured ProductVIEW BELL YORKThe View Bell York comes well equipped in height and features for any home.View ProductAbout usEstablished in 1974, Marble Hill Fireplaces offer the largest and most comprehensive selection of fireplaces in the UK. We have worked on many high profile projects including the refurbishment of Royal Residences and The Ritz and Savoy Hotels.Our ProductsAntique FireplacesStone fireplacesMarble FireplacesContemporary fireplacesBalanced Flue Gas FiresEnergy Efficient FiresFireplaces LondonBellfiresBarbas Wood FiresUseful LinksAbout usBlogTour our ShowroomsOur LocationCustomer ReviewsJob VacanciesOur BrochurePrivacy PolicyContact usMarble Hill Ltd 70-72 Richmond Road, Twickenham, Middlesex, TW1 3BE UK+44 (0)20 8892 1488info@marblehill.co.ukCopyright © 2017 Marble Hill Fireplaces Ltd. All Rights Reserved | Privacy PolicyWeb Design Surrey WOD.agency
